a2zsecure.com 2012-02-03

# A2Zsecure.com - Privacy Policy

| 

A2Z Secure views both privacy and data protection as important issues. Because of this, we have designed our Privacy Policy to explain how we handle personal information collected from merchants who deal with us for services and submit information to us through the Internet.  
  
---  
   
Privacy Policy Overview  
  
This Privacy Policy covers A2Z Secure’ treatment of personal information collected from merchants (hereafter "merchant" or "you") who use A2Z Secure’ services, as well as consumer information that is acquired in the course of business. This Policy also covers the treatment of personal information that A2Z Secure may share with business partners. This Policy does not apply to the practices of companies that A2Z Secure does not own or control or to people that A2Z Secure does not employ or manage.  

How Information is Collected and Used  
  
A2Z Secure collects your personal information when you register for an account, and when you use certain gateway products and services. A2Z Secure may also receive personal information from its resellers and other business partners. In the course of processing a payment transaction, we typically receive from the merchant, or a financial institution, information related to the transaction. This normally includes information about the payment that a consumer has furnished the merchant or financial institution in placing the order. 

The personal information we acquire when processing payment transactions varies but may include, for example, the amount of the transaction, the consumer's name, credit card number and expiration date, checking account number, billing address, and shipping address.

A2Z Secure uses the information collected to fulfill your requests for certain products and services, to process payment transactions, to facilitate billing, and otherwise deliver the payment gateway services. We may also send service announcements, newsletters, and periodic notices about specials and new products. Personal consumer information is used to process payment transactions and for no other purpose.  

Sharing and Disclosing Information  
  
Protecting personal information regarding merchants and consumers is an essential function of the gateway. A2Z Secure shares and discloses such information only as described below.  
A2Z Secure will send personal information about you to other companies or people when we have your consent to share the information and; 1) we need to share your information to provide the product or service you have requested; 2) we need to send the information to companies who work on behalf of A2Z Secure to provide a product or service to you. However, unless A2Z Secure tells you otherwise, these companies do not have any right to use your personal information we provide to them beyond what is necessary to assist us. 

A consumer’s personal information is shared with third parties (such as banks and credit card processors) to the extent necessary for A2Z Secure to provide payment-processing services. We also may release this information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with law; enforce or apply our Merchant Agreement and other agreements; or protect the rights, property, or safety of A2Z Secure, our users, or others. This includes exchanging information with other companies and organizations for fraud protection and risk reduction.  

Securing Information  
  
Because information security is critical to our business, we work to protect the security of your information during transmission by using Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) software, which encrypts information you input. A2Z Secure stores information gathered on secure computers located in a locked data center. The number of employees involved in the management of the data center that have physical access to these computers is limited, and we use firewalls and other security technology to prevent our computers from being accessed by unauthorized persons. Any personal consumer information sent to us by you should also be encrypted using SSL encryption.
